When did I become such a varietyist?
I looked back on my amazing life, and I was
I'm looking back on my life.
I wondered when and where I made the mistake.
I'm such a pain in the ass.
Even going to drink water during lessons.
I don't even go to drink water during lessons because it's a pain in the ass to walk.
He really is a pain in the ass.
Why did he quit?
My image is that I'm a really cool idol.
But surprisingly, I love cute things.
I think I'm more of a girl than anyone else.
I love cute things.
Idols and kettles
Hello! I'm Noma, from Stardust.
Oh, thank you very much for the sudden change.
Cute!
Yes, today, Unit 3 will be presenting again.
Yes, sir.
So, today's guest, I'm sure you've already heard his voice.
I'd like to call him up right away.
This is our idol, please!
Yes, I'm Hana Kojima from AmeFlash.
Thank you very much, Hana Kojima is here.
Here she is!
Kojima-san, you're Noma and Idol, you're Ichikawa-san from Ameyoko Kikaku and Miki's lyrics on location.
Yes.
She also participated in the interview with Japanese announcer Yoshida.
Yes, sir.
This is the first time for you to talk with Noma.
That's right.That's right.
I look forward to working with you today.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to start by asking you a few questions.
First of all, speaking of Ms. Hana Kojima...
I'm not sure about this, but on July 18th.
I'm not sure about this, but she's going to appear in a comedy event on July 18.
Thank you very much.
This...
At the time of the recording of the first report, the event had not yet taken place, and I think it will probably be over by the time this video is posted.
How did the offer come about?
Well, the staff has offered to put on a comedy competition for comedians only, and I've been asked to do it.
I got an offer. I was so surprised to find myself the only idol among all the comedians.
I wondered when I really became such a variety fan.
I wondered when and where I made that mistake... but I really did win that idol's big comedy event.
I don't know why I won, and I think that's probably because of that, but since I've been invited, I'd like to give it my all and do my best.
What was the reaction from the fans?
Well, the lineup is really strange, isn't it, comedians?
But when the announcement was made on sns, there were a lot of surprised voices like "Hana-chan in this group? I was surprised at her whininess.
I told everyone to laugh as hard as they could on that day because there were many people who were cheering for me to go and see the show.
It was very encouraging to see them laughing.
I told them to laugh no matter how funny it was.
How did your family react?
Well, my dad really loves that kind of thing, so he was very happy.
He said he wanted to participate in the last big comedy competition.
I'm thinking of asking him to participate this time instead of me.
He's a bit of a troubled father.
I think he's a wonderful father.
Yes, he is.
I think he posts something on Twitter every day.
How do you study this "big joke" on your own?How is this great pleasure of yours being studied independently?
I don't know if studying is the right word.
How do you train?
Well, I've never been to a comedy contest before, but I decided to enter one.
At the time of the idol competition...
I had never really done it before.
I was just trying to make a lot of guesses.
I put out a lot of material, as if I had a lot of hits.
But this time, I'm among comedians.
I'm really anxious about it.
I'm not sure if the daily comedy is helping me a little bit.
I think it's important to do it every day.
I'm going to do my best on my own.
Yes, whether it's idol activities or comedy.
I think it's important to accumulate things day by day.
That's right.
I'll do my best, and I'll be supporting you behind your back.
Thank you very much.
I really like this scene because it shows the coolness of the main character.
I really like the scene because it shows the coolness of the main character.
This show is about Ohana-san...
Puddin
Malik!
Aki Kurumada
This program was presented by local products!
Everyone keep on pushing the flowers!